Eric Shumway

148 Centerville Rd, Ridgeway SC 29130 (803) 719-6925

eric shumway@yahoo.com
linkedin.com/in/eric-shumway-493009228
https://github.com/eshumway1045
https://eshumway1045.github.io/Personal-Portfolio-2.0/

<u>Summary</u>

I currently have five years of experience in Retail and customer satisfaction. I am passionate about coding and love seeing all the ways coding can bring websites, and the user experience to life. I continue to enjoy learning how coding is evolving and the ways other coders' accomplishments make all of our lives easier, as well as looking for ways to be the one who changes how things are done.

Skills

- JavaScript
- MySQL
- HTML
- SQL
- Git
- MongoDB
- BootStrap

Projects

- Budgetek https://github.com/eshumway1045/Budgetek
- Simple day planner https://eshumway1045.github.io/simple-planner/

Experience

- 09/08/2019 to 02/01/2021
 - Product Flow Specialist, Best Buy
- 02/01/2021 to 05/09/2021
 - Product Flow Supervisor, Best Buy
- 05/09/2021 to current
 - Product Flow Specialist, Best Buy

Education and Training

Full Stack development bootcamp